Guide to Megan O'Shea's One Resource to Rule Them All MOS.2021
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Megan O'Shea's One Resource to Rule Them All
2016-2021, undated
2020-2021, undated
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Megan O'Shea
Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926
Belfrage family
Tamiment Library
Weatherly Stephan
MOS.2021
25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder 24" x 24"
This is the abstract. It has a title in it.
This is the physical facet of the collection.
10
Conditions Governing Access
This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
The following chronology provides a backdrop for the Board of Higher Education of the City of New York cases included within this collection:
1939 The New York State Legislature enacted Section 12-a of the Civil Service Law which provided in substance that "no person shall be appointed to or retained in the public service nor in any public educational institution who becomes a member of any organization which advocates the overthrow of government by force or violence, or by any unlawful means (L. 1939, Ch. 547)."
Abbreviation Expansion
MIT
Massachusetts Institute of Technology
PCV
Peace Corps Volunteer
Ordered List
This is a citation for Weatherly Stephan's Journal of Archival Organization article.
I don't know why on earth you'd put a line break in an ordered list,
but here ya go.
Copyright New York University, all rights reserved.
This is just a name name with no identity.
Accruals Note
This is the Accruals note.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
Appraisal
This is the Appraisal note.
Arrangement
This is the Arrangement note.
Biographical Note
This is the Biographical note.
Custodial History
This is the Custodial History note.
General
This is the General note.
Elmer Holmes Bobst Library
70 Washington Square South
2nd Floor
New York, NY 10012
special.collections@nyu.edu
URL:
ALS
The Sally Belfrage Papers (TAM 189)
Ardouin, Charles Nicholas Celigny. Essais sur l'histoire d'Haiti. Port-au-Prince, 1865.
No doubt the estate has exerted a tremendous influence on the development of my character. One may walk for an hour without glimpsing another soul, which has taught me to love tranquility.
Tamiment Library March 2021
Abbreviation Expansion
MIT
Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Oral histories (literary works) Rolodex MOS.2021 Fulbright scholars. Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.
Existence and Location of Originals
This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
Other Finding Aids
This is the Other Finding Aids note.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
Related Materials
This is the Related Materials note. Those using the collection may also be interested in P132, held in this repository, which includes photographs of Pemberly, Darcy's estate and childhood home. In an April 1795 letter to his friend, Charles Bingley, Darcy wrote
No doubt the estate has exerted a tremendous influence on the development of my character. One may walk for an hour without glimpsing another soul, which has taught me to love tranquility.
The Sally Belfrage Papers (TAM 189)
Scope and Content
This is the Scope and Content note.
Separated Materials
This is the Separated Materials note.
Existence and Location of Copies
This is the Existence and Location of Copies note.
Bibliography
This is the Bibliography.
Adler, Jerry. High Rise.New York:
Harper Collins, 1993.
Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry. Interim Report by the New York State Organized Crime Task Force. Ithaca, NY: ILR Press, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University, 1988.
Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry. Final Report to Governor Mario M. Cuomo. Ronald Goldstock, Director, New York State Organized Crime Task Force. December 1989.
Ardouin, Charles Nicholas Celigny. Essais sur l'histoire d'Haiti. Port-au-Prince, 1865.
Boston (Mass.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.; Oral histories (literary works); Fulbright scholars.; War Powers Conference; New York Nichibei.; Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926; Tamiment Library
- Level 2 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2015-2016; mos_2021_2; 80 Washington Square East Galleries; Blaustein Family; Aaron, Florence; 23 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder handwritten notes 24" x 24"; Level 2 This is the abstract. It has a bold title in it.; Level 2 This is the Materials Specific Details. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Level 2 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
  Accruals
  Level 2 This is the Accruals note.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Level 2 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
  Appraisal
  Level 2 This is the Appraisal note.
  Arrangement
  Level 2 This is the Arrangement note.
  Historical Note
  Level 2 This is the Historical note.
  Custodial History
  Level 2 This is the Custodial History note.
  File Plan
  Level 2 This is the File Plan.
  General
  This is the Level 2 General note.
  Elmer Holmes Bobst Library
  70 Washington Square South
  2nd Floor
  New York, NY 10012
  special.collections@nyu.edu
  URL:
  ALS
  The Sally Belfrage Papers (TAM 189)
  Ardouin, Charles Nicholas Celigny. Essais sur l'histoire d'Haiti. Port-au-Prince, 1865.
  No doubt the estate has exerted a tremendous influence on the development of my character. One may walk for an hour without glimpsing another soul, which has taught me to love tranquility.
  Tamiment Library March 2021
  Abbreviation Expansion
  MIT
  Massachusetts Institute of Technology
  Oral histories (literary works) Rolodex MOS.2021 Fulbright scholars. Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.
  Other Finding Aids
  Level 2 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
  Existence and Location of Originals
  Level 2 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Level 2 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
  Related Materials
  Level 2 This is the Related Materials note.
  Scope and Contents
  Level 2 This is the Scope and Content note.
  Separated Materials
  Level 2 This is the Separated Materials note.
  This is the Index head.
  Level 2 This is the Index.
  Level 2 Index term 1
  Level 2 Index term 2
  Level 2 Index term 3
  Boston (Mass.) -- Intellectual life -- 20th century.; Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.; Oral histories (literary works); Fulbright scholars.; War Powers Conference; Tamiment Library; Belfrage family
  - Level 3 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2021; mos_2021_3; 9 to 5, National Association of Working Women (U.S.); Chen family; Adams, B. O.; 12 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder Hopefully perfectly this is correct 12" x 12"; Level 3 This is the Abstract. It has a bold title in it.; Level 3 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 3 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Level 3 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
    Level 3 This is the Accruals note.
    Level 3 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
    Level 3 This is the Appraisal note.
    Level 3 This is the Arrangement note.
    Biographical note
    Level 3 This is the Biographical note.
    Level 3 This is the Custodial History note.
    Level 3 This is the File Plan.
    This is the Level 3 General note.
    Level 3 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
    Level 3 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
    Level 3 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
    Level 3 This is the Related Materials note.
    Level 3 This is the Scope and Content note.
    Level 3 This is the Separated Materials note.
    Index head
    Level 3 This is the Index.
    Level 3 Index item
    - Level 4 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2017-2019; mos_2021_4; Yivo Institute for Jewish Research; Pinsof family; Zwillinger, Rhonda; 2 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder This is a test 1' x 27"; Level 4 This is the Abstract.It has a bold title in it.; Level 4 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 4 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Level 4 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
      Level 4 This is the Accruals note.
      Level 4 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
      Level 4 This is the Appraisal note.
      Level 4 This is the Arrangement note.
      Level 4 This is the Biographical note.
      Level 4 This is the Custodial History note.
      Level 4 This is the File Plan.
      This is the Level 4 General note.
      Level 4 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
      Level 4 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
      Level 4 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
      Level 4 This is the Related Materials note.
      Level 4 This is the Scope and Content note.
      Level 4 This is the Separated Materials note.
      Level 4 This is the Index.
      Level 4 Index item
      - Level 5 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2015-2019; mos_2021_5; World Trade Center (New York, N.Y.); Draper family; Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901; 5 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder This is still a test 7" x 45'; Level 5 This is the Abstract. It has a bold title in it.; Level 5 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 5 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Level 5 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
        Level 5 This is the Accruals note.
        Level 5 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
        Level 5 This is the Appraisal note.
        Level 5 This is the Arrangement note.
        Level 5 This is the Biographical note.
        Level 5 This is the Custodial History note.
        Level 5 This is the File Plan.
        This is the Level 5 General note.
        Level 5 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
        Level 5 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
        Level 5 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
        Level 5 This is the Related Materials note.
        Level 5 This is the Scope and Content note.
        Level 5 This is the Separated Materials note.
        Level 5 This is the Index.
        Level 5 Index Item
        - Level 6 Series I. Megan O'Shea; Rolodex on New York University Here is a title, 2020; mos_2021_6; Workers' Party of Ireland; Blaustein Family; Alum, Rolando A.; 3 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 flat file folder This is still a test 2" x 2"; Level 6 This is the Abstract. It has a title in it.; Level 6 This is the Materials Specific Details note.; Level 6 This is the Physical Description note. (Box 1, Folder 337)
          Level 6 This is the Conditions Governing Access note.
          Level 6 This is the Accruals note.
          Level 6 This is the Immediate Source of Acquisition note.
          Level 6 This is the Appraisal note.
          Level 6 This is the Arrangement note.
          Level 6 This is the Biographical note.
          Level 6 This is the Custodial History note.
          Level 6 This is the File Plan.
          This is the Level 6 General note.
          Level 6 This is the Other Finding Aids note.
          Level 6 This is the Existence and Location of Originals note.
          Level 6 This is the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note.
          Level 6 This is the Related Materials note.
          Level 6 This is the Scope and Content note.
          Level 6 This is the Separated Materials note.
          Level 6 This is the Index.
          Level 6 Index item
          - A File Nested Within a File, No Container, 1981-08-31
  - This is an item Here is a title. There is also a name. (Box 1)
    Bibliography
    This is Not It: Stories. New York: Distributed Art Publishers, 2002.
  - The Dreaded Other Level, 1981-09-02
- Series II. Additional Digital Objects
  - Audio-Service
  - Audio-Reading-Room
  - Video-Service
  - Video-Reading-Room
  - Image-Service
  - External-Link
  - Electronic-Records-Reading-Room
  - Image-Service